# Xuanyu Peng

ODOFYPXY | home.dofy.top | dofypxy@pku.edu.cn | +86.198.0118.9807

#### Вю

I'm Xuanyu Peng, an undergraduate student from Turing Class, Peking University. I am now a member of Programming Language Lab, supervised by Prof. Yingfei Xiong. My research interests include program synthesis, program verification and blockchain security. I am also interning at Veridise, a company that provides a solution for hardening the security of the blockchain ecosystem.

#### Research Experience

#### Program Languages Lab, Peking University

Mar 2021 - present

Research assistant, supervised by Prof. Yingfei Xiong

Topics: Synthesizing Efficient Memoization Algorithms from Logical Specification

Veridise Inc. May 2022 - present

Research intern, supervised by Prof. Isil Dillig and Prof. Yu Feng

Topics: Formal Verification on Smart Contracts

#### EDUCATION

Peking University

Beijing, China

Turing Class, Bachelor of Science in Computer Science & Technology

Sep 2019 - present

GPA: 3.812/4.0 (rank: 12th/200)

## PROJECTS

#### Synthesizing Efficient Memoization Algorithms from Logical Specification

- First to formalized core concepts of memoization.
- Proposed a framework of automatic synthesis of effective memoization algorithm given declarative logical specification.
- The solutions to many classic algorithmic problems such as the Longest Common Sequence and 01-Knapsack can be synthesized.

Advisor: Yingfei Xiong. Collaborator: Yican Sun

#### Medjai: Symbolic Reasoning for Starknet/Cairo dApps

Link to Demo

- Execute Cairo program with symbolic inputs and explore all its possible program states.
- Automatically check whether certain properties hold on Cairo program.

Advisor: Isil Dillig. Collaborator: Yanju Chen, Jacob Van Geffen, Shankara Pailoor

#### A Dataset of Formalized Algorithmic Problem (use Minizinc)

- Formalized 50+ problems from NOIP-J/S (Chinese National Olympiad of Informatics for Junior/Senior High School Students).
- The final goal of dataset size is 200+.

Advisor: Yingfei Xiong. Collaborator: Siyuan Li

#### Scholarships and Awards

Gold Award (7th place), The 44th ACM-ICPC Asia Regionals Xuzhou Site	2019
Silver Award, The 5th CCPC Xiamen Site	2019
Peking University Third-Class Scholarship	2020
Peking University Three Good Student	2020
Ubiquant Scholarship	2021
John Hopcroft's Scholarship	2022

### SKILLS

Programming Languages C/C++, Python, Java, Coq, Racket, LaTeX